https://www.proscale.com/privacy-policy

Home
AboutProductsSearch by IndustryWoodworking & CabinetsMetalworkingPlasticsGlassAutomotiveAerospaceCustom DesignsMedical ApplicationsOur Product FamiliesLinear Encoder SystemsQuality ControlData Acquisition & InterfacesWired Data AcquisitionWireless Data AcquisitionSoftwareProduction And SetupIndividual ComponentsDigital ReadoutsScalesModel 150 Absolute ScalesModel 150G Absolute ScalesModel 250 Absolute ScalesModel 250G Absolute ScalesModel 190 Incremental ScalesModel 290 Incremental ScalesModel 390 Incremental ScalesModel 590 Incremental ScalesEncodersProScale Absolute
EncodersProScale Absolute "G" EncodersProScale Inductive EncodersMiscellaneous PartsSupportProduct BulletinsCase StudiesProduct ManualsProduct Presentations & DemosSoftwareFAQTestimonialsShipping & ReturnsWarrantyGlossaryContactWhere to Buy
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
You can visit Accurate Technology, Inc. websites to read product information, use the on-line tools, etc. without revealing any personal information. The only information we collect and store during normal web site usage is your IP address, the web-site that referred you to us, and the pages you request along with the date and time of those requests. We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of our services. During normal web-site usage we do not collect or store personally identifiable information such as name, e-mail address, phone number, mailing address, or any other information.
Personally identifiable information is ONLY collected when a purchase is made and that information is submitted by the individual making the purchase. It is retained for customer service purposes to verify you as an Accurate Technology, Inc. customer and for tracking of information. This information will NEVER be made available or distributed to other companies or agencies for any reason.
Copyright Information
All Site Content is copyright © 2000-2019 by Accurate Technology, Inc. The ProScale and Digi-Kit logos and name, the Accurate Technology, Inc. logos and name, as well as all other original or derivative artwork and marks on this site are protected by international law. No part of this web site may be reproduced in any way without the expressed written permission of the site owner.
The information contained herein is designed to be as comprehensive and factual as possible. We reserve the right, however, to make changes at any time without notice.
Some links provided in Accurate Technology, Inc. websites may lead to sites furnished by independent site owners. The information and/or recommendations presented therein are the sole responsibility of those site owners. Accurate Technology, Inc. has no control or responsibility for the content of those independent sites, only providing these links to its visitors for their convenience.
1-828-654-7920
Menu
Home
About
Products
Support
Contact
Where to Buy
Copyright © 2019 Accurate Technology Inc.
Website by integritive, inc. Web Design :: Asheville NC
